Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, negatives, and Scientific Baseball (manual), 1870 -- 2013; 1950 -- 1990; UA046.003; 29.8 Linear Feet; 490 Digital Object(s)
  - Daryl Brown Receives Houston Award, 1977; UA046.003.173.00041 (Box 173)
  - Campus and Staff Photos, 1970 -- 2000; UA046.003.173.00042 (Box 173)
  - Claffee and Men's Basketball, Athlete Headshots, assorted sports, 1960 -- 1970; UA046.003.173.00043 (Box 173)
  - Women's Crew 2nd Varsity Team Photo, 1994; UA046.003.174.00001 (Box 174)
  - Crew, 2000; UA046.003.174.00002 (Box 174)
  - Crew, 2000; UA046.003.174.00003 (Box 174)
  - Men's Crew Team Pix, 1985; UA046.003.174.00004 (Box 174)
  - Loose Crew Photos, 1970 -- 2000; UA046.003.174.00005 (Box 174)
  - Men's Crew, 1970 -- 2000; UA046.003.174.00006 (Box 174)
  - Cross Country, 1996; UA046.003.174.00007 (Box 174)
  - Men's and Women's Lacrosse, 1999; UA046.003.174.00008 (Box 174)
  - Cross Country Prints, 2001; UA046.003.174.00009 (Box 174)
  - Cross Country, 2000; UA046.003.174.00010 (Box 174)
  - Cross Country Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.174.00011 (Box 174)
  - Men's Cross Country, 2000; UA046.003.174.00012 (Box 174)
  - Men's Cross Country photos, 2000; UA046.003.174.00013 (Box 174)
  - Men's and Women's Lacrosse, 2000; UA046.003.174.00014 (Box 174)
  - Men's and Women's Lacrosse, 2000; UA046.003.174.00015 (Box 174)
  - Men's and Women's Lacrosse, 2000; UA046.003.174.00016 (Box 174)
  - Women's and Men's Cross Country Team Pix, 2000; UA046.003.174.00017 (Box 174)
  - C. W. Packsports Proof Sheets, Football and Men's Soccer, 2000; UA046.003.174.00018 (Box 174)
  - C. W. Packsports Proof Sheets, Men's and Women's Lacrosse and Baseball, 2000; UA046.003.174.00019 (Box 174)
  - C. W. Pack Proof Sheets, Various Sports, 2000; UA046.003.174.00020 (Box 174)
  - Event photos folder 1 of 2, 2000; UA046.003.174.00021 (Box 174)
  - Event photos folder 2 of 2, 2000; UA046.003.174.00022 (Box 174)
  - Fencing, 2003; UA046.003.174.00023 (Box 174)
  - Fencing, 2003; UA046.003.174.00024 (Box 174)
  - Fencing, 2003; UA046.003.174.00025 (Box 174)
  - Tufts Field Hockey Team Photograph, 1979; UA046.003.174.00026 (Box 174)
  - Tufts Field Hockey Team Photograph, 1980; UA046.003.174.00027 (Box 174)
  - Women's Field Hockey Team Photos, 1981 -- 1988; UA046.003.174.00028 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Pictures, 1985; UA046.003.174.00029 (Box 174)
  - Picture Field Hockey, 1986; UA046.003.174.00030 (Box 174)
  - Junior Class Field Hockey, 1989; UA046.003.174.00031 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Photo, 1990; UA046.003.174.00032 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Photo, 1992; UA046.003.174.00033 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Photo, 1994; UA046.003.174.00034 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photo, 1994; UA046.003.174.00035 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1995; UA046.003.174.00036 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Photo, 1995; UA046.003.174.00037 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photo, 1996; UA046.003.174.00038 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photo, 1997; UA046.003.174.00039 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1997; UA046.003.174.00040 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1997; UA046.003.174.00041 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1997; UA046.003.174.00042 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1997; UA046.003.174.00043 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1997; UA046.003.174.00044 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photo, 1998; UA046.003.174.00045 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photo, 1999; UA046.003.174.00046 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photo, 2000; UA046.003.174.00047 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.174.00048 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 2001; UA046.003.174.00049 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey [binder], 2000; UA046.003.174.00050 (Box 174)
  - Women's Field Hockey Team Photos, 2000; UA046.003.174.00051 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey Team Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.174.00052 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 2000; UA046.003.174.00053 (Box 174)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00001 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 1990; UA046.003.175.00002 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00003 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00004 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00005 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00006 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00007 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.175.00008 (Box 175)
  - Field Hockey, 2010; UA046.003.175.00009 (Box 175)
  - Varsity Football Team Photograph, 1958; UA046.003.175.00010 (Box 175)
  - Varsity Football Team Photograph, 1959; UA046.003.175.00011 (Box 175)
  - Football Squad Photograph, 1960; UA046.003.175.00012 (Box 175)
  - Football Squad Photograph, 1961; UA046.003.175.00013 (Box 175)
  - Football Squad Photograph, 1962; UA046.003.175.00014 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1964; UA046.003.175.00015 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1965; UA046.003.175.00016 (Box 175)
  - Varsity Team Photograph, 1968; UA046.003.175.00017 (Box 175)
  - Varsity Football Team Photograph, 1969; UA046.003.175.00018 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1971; UA046.003.175.00019 (Box 175)
  - Football Squad Team Photograph, 1973; UA046.003.175.00020 (Box 175)
  - Football Squad Team Photograph, 1974; UA046.003.175.00021 (Box 175)
  - Football Squad Photograph, 1975; UA046.003.175.00022 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1976; UA046.003.175.00023 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1978; UA046.003.175.00024 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1984; UA046.003.175.00025 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1985; UA046.003.175.00026 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1986; UA046.003.175.00027 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1989; UA046.003.175.00028 (Box 175)
  - Football Team Photograph, 1992; UA046.003.175.00029 (Box 175)
  - Football, 1992; UA046.003.175.00030 (Box 175)
  - Football - individual shots, 1993; UA046.003.175.00031 (Box 175)
  - J Football, 1993; UA046.003.175.00032 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots, 1995; UA046.003.175.00033 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots, 1997; UA046.003.175.00034 (Box 175)
  - Tufts Colby Football, 1998; UA046.003.175.00035 (Box 175)
  - Football, 1999; UA046.003.175.00036 (Box 175)
  - Football Fall, 1999; UA046.003.175.00037 (Box 175)
  - Football, 1999; UA046.003.175.00038 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.175.00039 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.175.00040 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00041 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00042 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00043 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00044 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00045 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00046 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2001; UA046.003.175.00047 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2002; UA046.003.175.00048 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2002; UA046.003.175.00049 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2003; UA046.003.175.00050 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2003; UA046.003.175.00051 (Box 175)
  - Football, 2010; UA046.003.175.00052 (Box 175)
  - Mens Football Team Photo, 2010; UA046.003.175.00053 (Box 175)
  - Carzo Eras Older Teams Football, 1960 -- 1980; UA046.003.175.00054 (Box 175)
  - Carzo and Two Football Players, 1973; UA046.003.175.00055 (Box 175)
  - Do Not Pass Photograph, 1970; UA046.003.175.00056 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.175.00057 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.175.00058 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.175.00059 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots and group photos, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.175.00060 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots and group photos, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.175.00061 (Box 175)
  - Football headshots and group photos, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.175.00062 (Box 175)
  - Individual Football player photographs, 1960 -- 1969; UA046.003.175.00063 (Box 175)
  - Individual Football player photographs, 1970 -- 1979; UA046.003.175.00064 (Box 175)
  - Football individual shots, coaches, staff, players, 1994; UA046.003.176.00001 (Box 176)
  - Football negatives, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.003.176.00002 (Box 176)
  - Football undated negatives, 1990 -- 2013; UA046.003.176.00003 (Box 176)
  - Football Sanko ford 1 of 2, 1990 -- 2003; UA046.003.176.00004 (Box 176)
  - Football Sanko ford 2 of 2, 1988 -- 1994; UA046.003.176.00005 (Box 176)
  - Football staff shots, 1990; UA046.003.176.00006 (Box 176)
  - Football teams, coaches, 1996; UA046.003.176.00007 (Box 176)
  - Football team pictures, 1973 -- 1999; UA046.003.176.00008 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990 -- 2000; UA046.003.176.00009 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990; UA046.003.176.00010 (Box 176)
  - Football, 2000 -- 2013; UA046.003.176.00011 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1995 -- 2010; UA046.003.176.00012 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990 -- 2000; UA046.003.176.00013 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1992; UA046.003.176.00014 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1980 -- 1999; UA046.003.176.00015 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990 -- 1999; UA046.003.176.00016 (Box 176)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.176.00017 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990 -- 2005; UA046.003.176.00018 (Box 176)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.176.00019 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1993; UA046.003.176.00020 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990 -- 1999; UA046.003.176.00021 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1998; UA046.003.176.00022 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1985 -- 1993; UA046.003.176.00023 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1986 -- 2006; UA046.003.176.00024 (Box 176)
  - Fottball, 2005 -- 2010; UA046.003.176.00025 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1998; UA046.003.176.00026 (Box 176)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.176.00027 (Box 176)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.176.00028 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1980 -- 1999; UA046.003.176.00029 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990 -- 2000; UA046.003.176.00030 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1988; UA046.003.176.00031 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1990; UA046.003.176.00032 (Box 176)
  - Football, 1980 -- 1999; UA046.003.176.00033 (Box 176)
  - Mens Football and various sports, 1943 -- 1990; UA046.003.176.00034 (Box 176)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.177.00001 (Box 177)
    photos
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.177.00002 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1995; UA046.003.177.00003 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1995; UA046.003.177.00004 (Box 177)
    negatives
  - Football, 1995; UA046.003.177.00005 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1995; UA046.003.177.00006 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1995; UA046.003.177.00007 (Box 177)
    Black and White Proof Copies
  - Football, 1996; UA046.003.177.00008 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1990; UA046.003.177.00009 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1990; UA046.003.177.00010 (Box 177)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.177.00011 (Box 177)
  - Football, 2000; UA046.003.177.00012 (Box 177)
    photos: individual shots
  - Football, 1996; UA046.003.177.00013 (Box 177)
  - Football, 1995; UA046.003.177.00014 (Box 177)
  - Gantcher Center Field House Opening Photo Album [1 of 2], 1999; UA046.003.177.00015 (Box 177)
    photos and slides
  - Gantcher Center Field House Opening Photo Album [2 of 2], 1999; UA046.003.177.00016 (Box 177)
  - Golf Team Photgraphs, 1960; UA046.003.177.00017 (Box 177)
  - Golf Team Pix, 1959 -- 1988; UA046.003.177.00018 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.003.177.00019 (Box 177)
    photos and negatives
  - Hockey, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.003.177.00020 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.003.177.00021 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 2001; UA046.003.177.00022 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 2004; UA046.003.177.00023 (Box 177)
  - Men's Ice Hockey Team Pix, 1985 -- 2007; UA046.003.177.00024 (Box 177)
    photos, negatives, proofs
  - Hockey, 1995; UA046.003.177.00025 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 1995; UA046.003.177.00026 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 2003; UA046.003.177.00027 (Box 177)
    photo and negatives
  - Hockey, 1990; UA046.003.177.00028 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 1989; UA046.003.177.00029 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 1993; UA046.003.177.00030 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 1993; UA046.003.177.00031 (Box 177)
    photos and black and white proof copies
  - Hockey, 1993; UA046.003.177.00032 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 1993; UA046.003.177.00033 (Box 177)
  - Hockey, 2003; UA046.003.177.00034 (Box 177)
    photos and negative
  - Ice Hockey, 1987; UA046.003.177.00035 (Box 177)
  - Homecoming Weekend, 1995; UA046.003.177.00036 (Box 177)
    contact sheets
  - Lacrosse Photograph, 1953; UA046.003.177.00037 (Box 177)
    photo
  - Undated Lacrosee Team Photo, 1994; UA046.003.177.00038 (Box 177)
    photo, Women's Lacrosse
  - Lacrosee Team Photo, 1997; UA046.003.177.00039 (Box 177)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1997 -- 2002; UA046.003.177.00040 (Box 177)
  - Lacrosse Team Photo, 1998; UA046.003.177.00041 (Box 177)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1998; UA046.003.177.00042 (Box 177)
  - Lacrosse Team Photo, 2000; UA046.003.177.00043 (Box 177)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2002 -- 2006; UA046.003.177.00044 (Box 177)
    team photos
  - 1953 Lacrosse Reunion Photographs, 2003; UA046.003.177.00045 (Box 177)
  - 1953 Lacrosse 50th Reunion Photograph (May 16, 2003), UA046.003.177.00046 (Box 177)
  - Men's Lacrosse Team Pix, 1945 -- 2006; UA046.003.177.00047 (Box 177)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1994 -- 2006; UA046.003.178.00001 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1990 -- 2000; UA046.003.178.00002 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1996 -- 2000; UA046.003.178.00003 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse and football, 1997 -- 2001; UA046.003.178.00004 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1995 -- 2005; UA046.003.178.00005 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2001; UA046.003.178.00006 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1950 -- 2002; UA046.003.178.00007 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000 -- 2005; UA046.003.178.00008 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1997; UA046.003.178.00009 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1950 -- 1989; UA046.003.178.00010 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1983 -- 2000; UA046.003.178.00011 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2001 -- 2003; UA046.003.178.00012 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1990 -- 2000; UA046.003.178.00013 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000; UA046.003.178.00014 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2001; UA046.003.178.00015 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1997 -- 2003; UA046.003.178.00016 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.003.178.00017 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000; UA046.003.178.00018 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.003.178.00019 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.003.178.00020 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 2000 -- 2009; UA046.003.178.00021 (Box 178)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1990 -- 2000; UA046.003.178.00022 (Box 178)
  - Men's and women's lacrosse, 1971 -- 1983; UA046.003.178.00023 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse team photos, 1982 -- 2010; UA046.003.178.00024 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1998; UA046.003.178.00025 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse, 2000; UA046.003.178.00026 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse 1 of 2, 2002; UA046.003.178.00027 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse 2 of 2, 2002; UA046.003.178.00028 (Box 178)
  - Lacrosse photo, 2008; UA046.003.178.00029 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse slides and photos Allan Clemow, 1975 -- 1983; UA046.003.178.00030 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse team fix 1 of 2, 1985 -- 2006; UA046.003.178.00031 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse team fix 2 of 2, 1976 -- 1994; UA046.003.178.00032 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse photos, 1980 -- 2003; UA046.003.178.00033 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse photos, 1997 -- 2003; UA046.003.178.00034 (Box 178)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1980 -- 1990; UA046.003.178.00035 (Box 178)
  - Tim Ring, Lacrosse coach, 1960 -- 1964; UA046.003.178.00036 (Box 178)
  - Debbi Milligan team photos, 1998 -- 2007; UA046.003.178.00037 (Box 178)
  - NCAA football rules committee, including Carzo, 1980; UA046.003.178.00038 (Box 178)
  - Passing of the ashes Homecoming, 1999; UA046.003.178.00039 (Box 178)
  - Pop Houston Award, 1972 -- 1973; UA046.003.178.00040 (Box 178)
  - Photo of Rocky Carzo and John DiBiaggio, 1992 -- 2001; UA046.003.178.00041 (Box 178)
  - Rocky's reception proof sheets, 1999; UA046.003.178.00042 (Box 178)
  - SAAC play day, 2000; UA046.003.178.00043 (Box 178)
  - Sailing, 1974; UA046.003.179.00001 (Box 179)
  - Sailing Contact Sheets, 1996; UA046.003.179.00002 (Box 179)
  - Sailing (Large Neg.), 1996 -- 2003; UA046.003.179.00003 (Box 179)
  - Sailing Photo and Negative, 2000; UA046.003.179.00004 (Box 179)
    photo and negative
  - Sailing Photos, 2003; UA046.003.179.00005 (Box 179)
    photos and CD-ROM
  - Sailing Team Photographs, 1966 -- 1978; UA046.003.179.00006 (Box 179)
  - Merrill Shea Photo Series Information, 1999; UA046.003.179.00007 (Box 179)
    letter and non-Tufts Sports photos
  - Tufts Soccer Action, 1998; UA046.003.179.00008 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA046.003.179.00009 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Team Pix, 1980 -- 2007; UA046.003.179.00010 (Box 179)
    team photos and negatives
  - M Soccer, 1980 -- 1992; UA046.003.179.00011 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs: Debi Milligan, 2000; UA046.003.179.00012 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer: Loose Photographs, 1989 -- 1997; UA046.003.179.00013 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.179.00014 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.179.00015 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.179.00016 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.179.00017 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 1997 -- 2003; UA046.003.179.00018 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 2000; UA046.003.179.00019 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 1998; UA046.003.179.00020 (Box 179)
  - Men's Soccer Photographs, 2001; UA046.003.179.00021 (Box 179)
  - Randee Mc Ardle (Women's Soccer), 2000; UA046.003.179.00022 (Box 179)
    individual photos
  - Play-Off Prints Binder: Women's Soccer, 1993; UA046.003.179.00023 (Box 179)
  - Team Photos (Women's Soccer), 1989 -- 1995; UA046.003.179.00024 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer, 1995; UA046.003.179.00025 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer, 2000; UA046.003.179.00026 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer, 2000; UA046.003.179.00027 (Box 179)
  - W Soc NCAAs, 2000; UA046.003.179.00028 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer, 2002; UA046.003.179.00029 (Box 179)
  - Women's Team Photograph, 2005; UA046.003.179.00030 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer Team Pix [1 of 2], 1996 -- 2004; UA046.003.179.00031 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer Team Pix [2 of 2], 1980 -- 2007; UA046.003.179.00032 (Box 179)
    photos and contact sheets
  - W Soccer, 1986; UA046.003.179.00033 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer Photos, 1982 -- 2000; UA046.003.179.00034 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer Photographs, 1998; UA046.003.179.00035 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer, 2001; UA046.003.179.00036 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer, 2000; UA046.003.179.00037 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer Photographs, 1997 -- 2003; UA046.003.179.00038 (Box 179)
  - W Soccer, 1998; UA046.003.179.00039 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer, 1995; UA046.003.179.00040 (Box 179)
  - Women's Soccer, 2000; UA046.003.179.00041 (Box 179)
  - Softball, 1985 -- 1989; UA046.003.179.00042 (Box 179)
  - Softball, 1990 -- 1994; UA046.003.179.00043 (Box 179)
  - Softball, 1995 -- 1999; UA046.003.180.00001 (Box 180)
  - Softball, 1997; UA046.003.180.00002 (Box 180)
  - Softball Team Photos, 2003; UA046.003.180.00003 (Box 180)
  - Softball, 2000 -- 2004; UA046.003.180.00004 (Box 180)
  - Softball, 2001; UA046.003.180.00005 (Box 180)
  - Softball, 2002; UA046.003.180.00006 (Box 180)
  - Softball, 2005 -- 2010; UA046.003.180.00007 (Box 180)
  - Softball team photos and baby pictures, 1970 -- 1995; UA046.003.180.00008 (Box 180)
  - Softball Team Pix, 1975 -- 2005; UA046.003.180.00009 (Box 180)
  - Softball Team Loose Photographs, 1985 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00010 (Box 180)
  - Softball Photographs, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00011 (Box 180)
  - Softball Photographs, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00012 (Box 180)
  - Softball Photographs, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00013 (Box 180)
  - Women's Softball photos, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00014 (Box 180)
  - Women's Softball photos, 2005; UA046.003.180.00015 (Box 180)
  - Sports Medicine Staff Photos, 2000; UA046.003.180.00016 (Box 180)
  - Men's Squash, 1998; UA046.003.180.00017 (Box 180)
  - Men's and Women's Squash, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00018 (Box 180)
  - Softball Team, 2000; UA046.003.180.00019 (Box 180)
  - Squash Team Photographs and Negatives, 1995 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00020 (Box 180)
  - Men's and Women's Squash Team Pix, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.003.180.00021 (Box 180)
  - Women's Squash Team, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.003.180.00022 (Box 180)
  - Men's and Women's Squash, 1999; UA046.003.180.00023 (Box 180)
  - Men's and Women's Squash, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.003.180.00024 (Box 180)
  - Men's and Women's Squash, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.003.180.00025 (Box 180)
  - Women's Squash, 2000 -- 2010; UA046.003.180.00026 (Box 180)
  - Swimming Team Photo, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.180.00027 (Box 180)
  - Swimming Team Photo, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.180.00028 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.180.00029 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1980 -- 1981; UA046.003.180.00030 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1981 -- 1982; UA046.003.180.00031 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1982 -- 1983; UA046.003.180.00032 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1983 -- 1984; UA046.003.180.00033 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1984 -- 1985; UA046.003.180.00034 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1985 -- 1986; UA046.003.180.00035 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1986 -- 1987; UA046.003.180.00036 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1987 -- 1988; UA046.003.180.00037 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.003.180.00038 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.003.180.00039 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.003.180.00040 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1991 -- 1992; UA046.003.180.00041 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1992 -- 1993; UA046.003.180.00042 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.003.180.00043 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.003.180.00044 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.003.180.00045 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photos, 1996 -- 1997; UA046.003.180.00046 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photos, 1997 -- 1998; UA046.003.180.00047 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photos, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.003.180.00048 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photos, 1999 -- 2000; UA046.003.180.00049 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photos, 2000 -- 2001; UA046.003.180.00050 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.003.180.00051 (Box 180)
  - Swim and Dive, 2001 -- 2002; UA046.003.180.00052 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2002 -- 2003; UA046.003.180.00053 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2003 -- 2004; UA046.003.180.00054 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2004 -- 2005; UA046.003.180.00055 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2005 -- 2006; UA046.003.180.00056 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2006 -- 2007; UA046.003.180.00057 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2007 -- 2008; UA046.003.180.00058 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2010 -- 2011; UA046.003.180.00059 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Photo, 2011 -- 2012; UA046.003.180.00060 (Box 180)
  - Swim Team Photographs - Men, 1970 -- 1999; UA046.003.180.00061 (Box 180)
  - Men's Swimming, 1970 -- 2007; UA046.003.180.00062 (Box 180)
  - Swim Team Photographs - Women, 1976 -- 1980; UA046.003.180.00063 (Box 180)
  - Women's Swimming Team Pix, 1970 -- 2000; UA046.003.181.00001 (Box 181)
  - Women's Swimming, 1970 -- 1980; UA046.003.181.00002 (Box 181)
  - Swim Team, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.181.00003 (Box 181)
  - Swim Team, 1980 -- 2000; UA046.003.181.00004 (Box 181)
  - Men's Tennis, 1997; UA046.003.181.00005 (Box 181)
  - Men's Tennis, 1997; UA046.003.181.00006 (Box 181)
  - Men's Tennis, 1997; UA046.003.181.00007 (Box 181)
  - Men's Tennis, 1997; UA046.003.181.00008 (Box 181)
  - Men's Tennis, 2002; UA046.003.181.00009 (Box 181)
  - Men's Tennis Team Pix, 1981; UA046.003.181.00010 (Box 181)